### www.linkedin.com/in/vzottmann

# Victor Zottmann

www.github.com/victorzottmann

## Frontend Developer

victor@victorzottmann.com

www.victorzottmann.com

#### **SUMMARY**

Dedicated frontend developer with one year of practical experience gained through internships. With a keen eye for design, Victor seeks to acquire further frontend skills to enhance interactions and elevate user experiences through innovative approaches.

#### **SKILLS**

### **Technical Skills:**

- Proficient: JavaScript, React, Node.js, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Git
- Familiar: TypeScript, C#, C++, Python, SQL, NoSQL, Jira, Confluence, Unit Testing

#### Soft Skills:

· Teamwork, Positive Attitude, Problem Solving, Strong Communication, Strong Work Ethic, Critical Thinking

#### **EMPLOYMENT**

## **Software Engineering Intern**

### **Audinate**

Dec 2022 - Feb 2023

- Facilitated development progress by successfully replacing a deprecated package responsible for managing file storage in MongoDB with an implementation of the GridFS API and Node.js streams.
- Wrote unit tests in the Mocha testing framework to validate the integrity of files that were uploaded and downloaded from a MongoDB database.

### **Software Engineering Intern**

#### **Audinate**

Mar 2022 - Sep 2022

- Improved an internal customer support platform by adding multi-language support using React Intl and React Context APIs with Typescript.
- Designed wireframes to improve the usability of the customer support platform.
- · Helped product owners and managers refine customer requirements by developing practical user stories.

### **Research and Development Intern**

#### **Audinate**

Aug 2021 - Mar 2022

- Collaborated with an external client in the testing of a proprietary desktop application.
- · Participated in the design thinking process and wireframe prototyping of a new product.

### **EDUCATION**

## Sydney, NSW

## **University of Technology Sydney**

Feb 2022 - Dec 2023

Master of Interaction Design (Extension) - Weighted Average Mark: 84.3 / 100

- Major: Interaction Programming
- Programming Coursework: Web Development, .NET Development, UNIX Systems, Python, Arduino Prototyping
- Awards: Dean's List 2023 (Engineering), LATAM International Postgraduate Coursework Scholarship

### RECENT PROJECTS

Personal Website: <u>www.victorzottmann.com</u> (for additional information and projects)

Car Rental System (Website: <a href="https://victorz-car-rental.netlify.app/">https://victorz-car-rental.netlify.app/</a>)

- Developed a website using HTML, CSS and JavaScript that allows users to rent cars on display.
- Utilized: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, Local Storage, Bootstrap.

## Arduino Memory Game (Demo: https://youtu.be/zJscLV0aoM8)

- Built a physical prototype of a memory game using Arduino and electronic components.
- Tested the product with real users to improve upon usability issues found in the first design iteration.
- Utilized: Arduino, C++, Soldering Tools.